Guide to the Turkish Photography Collection 1910-1990 AD.MC.007
AbuDhabi
- A group of men in football uniforms on a football pitch with their coach. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Sports; Turkey; Uniforms
- A family group seated on a balcony. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Children; Cigarettes; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- An older male wearing a costume in satin and a head-dress, from a play. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Costumes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Performance Plays; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Turkey
- Three males standing in front of palm trees, male in the middle has a mustache. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Mustaches; Photographic Prints; Trees; Turkey
- A mixed group of males and females seated at cafe tables on a gravel patio. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Cameras; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Turkey; Women
- A male in a dark suit sitting at a table writing, female in white dress standing at the desk with flower arrangements in the background. 9.2 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Flowers; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- Four females sitting on a flower patterned couch drinking out of small wine glasses. 8.5 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 10)
  Drinking; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- Constantinople and the Golden Horn. Constantinople - Corne d'Or et Stamboul. 8.7 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Beyazit Tower; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Suleymaniye Mosque; The Golden Horn
- Constantinople - Vue générale des Eaux-Douces d'Europe. 8.8 x 13.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; The Golden Horn
- Constantinople - Kiosk du Sultan aux eaux douces d'Asie. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Bosphorous; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Kucuksu Palace; Postcards
- General View of Istanbul. Istanbul manzarai umumiyesi. 9.1 x 14.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Bosphorous; Galata Bridge; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; The Golden Horn
- A train station in Algeria. 263 ALGER - La Route de Malakoff et la Gare de Bab-el-Oued. 8.7 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Algiers, Algeria; Postcards; Seas; Trains
- Constantinople - Mosquee Validé. Sultan Valide Mosque aka the New Mosque (Yeni Cami). 8.7 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Mosques; New Mosque; Postcards; Steamboats; Yeni Cami
- A boat on the Bosphorous in front of Rumeli Hisari Fortress. Le Bosphore devant Roumeli-Hissar. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Bosphorous; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Rumelihisari
- The Golden Horn. 35 Istanbul Haliç - La Corne d'Or. 8.8 x 14.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Beyazit Tower; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Suleymaniye Mosque; The Golden Horn
- A view of Rumelihisari and the Bosphorus. Vue des châteaux et des Eaux douces d'Asie au Bosphore. 8.7 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 11)
- The Turkish Cemetery in Scutari (Uskudar). Cimetière turc a Scutari. 8.3 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 11)
  Cemeteries; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Uskudar, Turkey
- The port of Constantinople. Constantinople - Vue Panoramique du Port. 8.7 x 13.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Bosphorous; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; The Golden Horn
- Bebek on the Bosphorous. Constantinople - Vue de Bébek Bosphore. 8.7 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Bebek, Istanbul, Turkey; Boats; Bosphorous; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Rumelihisari; Steamboats
- Suleymaniye Mosque and the Golden Horn. 152 Istanbul, Suleymaniye Camii ve Haliç - Mosq. Suleimaniye et la Corne d'Or. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Suleymaniye Mosque; The Golden Horn
- People on a ferris wheel with a Turkish flag in the background. 14.0 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Entertainment; Flags; Photographic Prints; Postcards; Turkey
- The Galata Bridge in Istanbul. Istanbul, Galata Köprüsü 192 - Le Pont. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Galata Bridge; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; The Golden Horn; Yeni Cami
- Sultan Ahmed Mosque (aka The Blue Mosque) and the Hippodrome. Mosquée de Sultan Ahmed et L'Hippodrome. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Blue Mosque; Constantinople; Hippodrome of Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Ottoman Writing; Postcards
- Yuksek-Kaldirim, a neighborhood in Istanbul. Salute de Constantinople - Yuksek-Kaldérim (neighborhood). 13.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Constantinople; Galata Tower; Postcards; Yuksek Kaldirim, Istanbul, Turkey
- Small boats on canals. Constantinople - Vue des Eaux-Douces d'Asie. 8.6 x 1.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Boats; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- Dolmabahce Palace. Constantinople - Palais de Dolma Bagtche. 8.5 x 13.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Bosphorous; Constantinople; Dolmabahce Palace; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- Boats in the port of Constantinople. Constantinople - Port de Constantinople. 8.6 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 12)
  Boats; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Ports; Postcards
- The interior of the Grand Bazaar. Constantinople - Intérieur du Grand Bazar. 8.7 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Constantinople; Grand Bazaar; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Shopkeepers
- The War Ministry Square/entrance of Istanbul University. Constantinople - Place du Séraskérat. 8.6 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Beyazit Tower; Constantinople; Istanbul University; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- Uskudar, Istanbul and the Bosphorous. Istanbul. Vue de Scutari au Bosphore. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Bosphorous; Cihangir, Beyoglu, Istanbul, Turkey; Istanbul, Turkey; Maiden's Tower; Postcards; Uskudar, Turkey
- Ortakoy Mosque. Mosque of Ortakeuï Constantinople. 8.7 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Bosphorous; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Ortakoy Mosque; Postcards
- The Ministry of War complex, now the entrance to Istanbul University. Constantinople - Minstére de la Guerre. 9.2 x 13.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 13)
- The Turkish Cemetery in Uskudar. Constantinople - Cimetiére turc a Scutari. 8.6 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Cemeteries; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- The Sunnet bridge in Kagithane. Constantinople. Eaux douces d'Europe. 8.6 x 13.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Boats; Constantinople; Kagithane, Istanbul, Turkey; Parks; Postcards
- The abolution fountain at the Yeni-Cami (New Mosque). Constantinople - Fountaine d'Ablutions a Jéni-Djami. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Constantinople; Head Covers; Istanbul, Turkey; New Mosque; Postcards; Yeni Cami
- Eyup Cemetery and the Golden Horn. Constantinople - Cimetiére d'Eyoub et La Corne d'Or. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Cemeteries; Constantinople; Eyup, Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; The Golden Horn
- Ortakoy Mosque. Salut de Constantinople - Mosquée Validé a Ortakeuy - Bosphore. 9.0 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 13)
  Boats; Bosphorous; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Mosques; Ortakoy Mosque; Postcards
- Column of Constantine (aka the Burnt Stone). 14.1 x 9.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Column of Constantine; Constantinople; Handtinting; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- Constantinople. Derwiches Tourneurs - Whirling Dervishes gathered on a large carpet with instruments. 8.8 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Constantinople; Dervishes; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- Two men sitting in a cemetery with large trees in the background. 8.6 x 13.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Constantinople - Mosquée du Sultan Ahmed et l'Hippodrome - The Mosque of Sultan Ahmed and the Hippodrome in Constantinople. 8.7 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Blue Mosque; Constantinople; Hippodrome of Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- 102 Constantinople - Int. de Ste. Sophia - Close up of the Hagia Sophia with large Ali medallion. 8.4 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Constantinople; Hagia Sophia; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- Constantinople - Stamboul au coucher du soleil - Bosphorous at sunset with Constantinople in the background. 9.0 x 14 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Beyazit Tower; Bosphorous; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Suleymaniye Mosque; The Golden Horn
- Constantinople - Vue Panoramique de la Mosquée Suleymanie - Panoramic view of the Suleymanie Mosque in Constantinople. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Suleymaniye Mosque; The Golden Horn
- 123 A Turkish barber shop in Constantinople - Overpainted colored postcard 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Shops
- Overpainted colored postcard of Constantinople. Arsenal Maritime - Imperial Arsenal or Tersâne-i Âmire was the main base and naval shipyard. Eyoub - Eyüp, in Istanbul. Kassim Pacha (Kasimpasa), Istanbul. 9.4 x 13.7 cm, 19 November 1947; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Constantinople; Eyup, Istanbul, Turkey; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; The Golden Horn
- Postcard. Jerusalem - Busy David Street - David Street in Jerusalem. 14.1 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
  Jerusalem; Postcards; Streets
- 52 Damas - La Forteresse - The Fortress/Citadel of Damascus, Syria. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Archaeological Sites; Damascus, Syria; Postcards
- Covered women walking along a cobbled stone street with tall stone buildings in the background. 14.1 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Postcards; Unknown Locations; Women
- 6240 Scénes et Types - Group de Mauresques - Postcard of three Moorish women in traditional dress. 8.9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Postcards; The Moors; Unknown Locations; Women
- Port Said - Main Street - Overpainted colored postcard. Main Street of Port Said, shops selling cigarettes. 9.0 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Port Said, Egypt; Postcards; Shopkeepers
- Môise springs at Suez - Môise Springs at Suez in Egypt. Date palms, people carrying water. Printed for Ar[...]ugheti Bros. Suez, Egypt. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Postcards; Suez, Egypt; Trees
- 18 Alexandria - Cherif Pacha Street - Sherif Pasha Street in Alexandria, Egypt with horse drawn carriages with buildings in the background. 8.8 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Alexandria, Egypt; Postcards; Streets
- 17 Alexandria - Mosque Attarine Street - Attarine mosque Street in Alexandria, Egypt 7.2 x 14.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Alexandria, Egypt; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Postcards; Streets
- Two men kneeling to pray with a camel in front of the Nile and the Pyramids of Giza. 8.8 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Alexandria, Egypt; Camels; Nile River; Postcards; Pyramids of Giza
- 69 Port Said - General View Town and Canal - General view of the town and canal of Port Said, Egypt. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Port Said, Egypt; Postcards
- Bedouin men and camels in the desert with a town in the background. Arabic writing. 8.8 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Arabic Writing; Bedouins; Camels; Postcards; Unknown Locations
- 64 Port Said - The Harbor - Three large ships in the harbour of Port Said, Egypt. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Port Said, Egypt; Ports; Postcards
- Caravan of camels walking along a tree lined road. 9.1 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Camels; Postcards; Trees; Unknown Locations; Women
- Three women in traditional dress with intricate head wraps. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Postcards; Traditional Dress; Unknown Locations; Women
- 1014 Femmes Arabes - Two Arab females sitting and standing in front of a intricately carved doorway. 14.4 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 16)
- 390 Belle Fatma - J. Geiser, Alger - A female in traditional dress. Algeria. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Algeria; Algiers, Algeria; Postcards; Traditional Dress; Women
- 6370 Scénes et Types - Femme Arabe voilée, Costume de Ville, Edition Sion-Bismuth, 9, Avenue de France, Tunis - A female with a dark face cover and light dress. 13.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Postcards; Traditional Dress; Tunis, Tunisia; Women
- Femme indigéne ouled nail - A female holding dates over her head and date palms in the background. 14.0 x 9.1 cm, 1930; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Postcards; Traditional Dress; Trees; Unknown Locations; Women
- 35. - Scénes et Types - Fillettes Kabyles - Two barefoot females standing in front of some crude houses. 13.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Girls; Postcards; Traditional Dress; Unknown Locations
- Ghardaia - Vue d'ensemble - A group of camels, mostly seated in front of a small hill-top town. Ghardaïa is the capital city of Ghardaïa Province, Algeria. 9.2 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Algeria; Camels; Postcards
- 826 Mauresque - A Moorish female covered in a white cloak with a dark dress underneath standing next to a body of water. 14.0 x 9.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Postcards; The Moors; Traditional Dress; Unknown Locations; Women
- 1093 Scénes et Types - La Belle Fatma, costume de femme Arabe riche - A female dress in traditional dress. 13.7 x 8.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Furnishings; Postcards; Traditional Dress; Unknown Locations; Women
- Two young females on a roof top looking out over Algiers. 13.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Algiers, Algeria; Girls; Postcards
- 83. Scénes et Types - Une fête Arabe, La danse des Foulards - A group of men gathered for a dance in an empty courtyard with houses in the background. 9.0 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Algeria; Dancing; Entertainment; Postcards
- Jew's wailing place - Jerusalem - Muraille de lamentation de Juifs - Jewish worshippers at the Wailing Wall. 9.0 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Jerusalem; Postcards
- 1136 Campement de nomades au desert - Bedouins in the desert in tents. 9.1 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Bedouins; Deserts; Postcards; Traditional Dress; Unknown Locations
- 145 ALGER - Rue du Palmier - Veiled women walking down a narrow cobbled street. Algiers, Algeria. 13.8 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Algiers, Algeria; Postcards; Women
- 6227 Scénes et Types - Intérieur Arabe - Woman pouring water from an animal hide bladder, seated woman using a grinding stone. 8.7 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Architecture; Men; Postcards; Unknown Locations; Women
- Damas - Rue de Barada - Old houses along a walled canal with trees. Damascus, Syria. 9.1 x 14.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Architecture; Damascus, Syria; Houses; Postcards; Rivers; Streets
- 8047 - Un Marabout dans l'extrême Sud Algérien - A woman in traditional dress holding a decorated water jug over her shoulder, palm trees in the background. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Algeria; Postcards; Traditional Dress; Women
- Damas - Vue générale du centre de la ville - A general view of the center of Damascus, Syria. 9.2 cm x 14.2 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Damascus, Syria; Postcards
- 1044 Scénes et Types - Réunion d'Aissaouas - A large group of men in traditional dress gathered around a man holding a musical instrument. 8.8 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Gatherings; Musical Instruments; Postcards; Traditional Dress; Unknown Locations
- Men in long light colored cloaks and head covers in front of stone walled buildings with palm trees and camels. 9.0 x 14.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Postcards; Traditional Dress; Unknown Locations
- 1142 Cairo - Shareh Bulak - Street view with cars, busses and pedestrians in Cairo, Egypt. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Cairo, Egypt; Cars; Postcards; Shops; Streets
- 14 Assuan - View from Cataract Hotel - a general view from the Cataract Hotel in Aswan, Egypt. Le nil à syène dans la region des cataractes - The Nile in Aswan (Syene) in the Cataract Region. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Aswan, Egypt; Hotels; Postcards
- 102T Noce Arabe - an Arab wedding ceremony. Girl in the center is seated on a chair in intricate robes and has a unibrow. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Postcards; Traditional Dress; Unknown Locations; Wedding Ceremony; Wedding Portraits
- Panorama de Jérusalem pris du Nord - a panoramic view of Jerusalem from the North. 9.0 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Négresse pétrissant la galette dans la Guessaá - a young girl kneading bread in Guessaá, Tunisia. Negress kneading dough in the Guessaá. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Architecture; Girls; Postcards; Tunisia
- 6194 Scenes et Types - Femme Nomade - a female in traditional dress holding a young child with a U.S. 2 cent postage stamp on it. 13.9 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Children; Postal Stamps; Postcards; Traditional Dress; Unknown Locations; Women
- Istanbul - Umumi bakisi (Vue générale) - a general view of Istanbul and the Bosphorous. 8.9 x 14.0 cm, 9 October 1938; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Bosphorous; Galata Bridge; Greek Writing; Istanbul, Turkey; New Mosque; Postcards; Tehran, Iran; Yeni Cami
- Constantinople - Fountaine de l'emperor Guillaume II - the Fountain of the Emperor William II in Constantinople.8.8 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Architecture; Blue Mosque; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Ottoman Writing; Postcards
- Constantinople - Tour de Léandre - the Leander/Maiden's Tower in Constantinople. Sinâsi Akbatu - Foto Arsivi. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, 12 October 1911; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Bosphorous; Constantinople; French Writing; Istanbul, Turkey; Maiden's Tower; Postcards
- 39 Constantinople - Mosquée de Sultan Ahmed - the Sultan Ahmed Mosque in Constantinople. 8.5 x 13.5 cm, 26 March 1923; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Blue Mosque; Constantinople; French Writing; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Postcards
- Istanbul - Galata Köprüsü - Le pont de Galata - the Galata Bridge in Istanbul. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, 3 June 1937; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Galata Bridge; Istanbul, Turkey; Postal Stamps; Postcards
- Topkapi Sarayi Müzesi - Arz Odasi, Salle d'audience - the Audience Hall in the Topkapi Palace in Istanbul, Turkey. 8.8 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Architecture; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards; Topkapi Palace
- Constantinople - Vue Panoramique des Bazaars - a panoramic view of the bazaars in Constantinople. 8.7 x 13.9 cm, 29 August 1921; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Constantinople; Grand Bazaar; Istanbul, Turkey; Market Places; Ottoman Writing; Postcards
- Souvenir de Brousse - Interieur de la Mosquée Oulou, Le Mihrab - the Mihrab of the Grand Mosque in Bursa, Turkey. 13.9 x 9.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Bursa, Turkey; Mosques; Ottoman Writing; Postal Stamps; Postcards
- The Tower of the Rumeli-Hisar Castle and the Bosphorous, Istanbul. 8.9 x 14.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Bosphorous; Istanbul, Turkey; Ottoman Writing; Postcards; Rumelihisari
- 6087 Scenes et Types - Groupes de Femmes Bédouines - Three Bedouin females and three small children. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Bedouins; Children; Postcards; Unknown Locations; Women
- Mariage arabe - An Arab marriage with a procession of camels. 9.0 x 14.1 cm, 1926; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Camels; Florence, Italy; Italian Writing; Postal Stamps; Postcards; Unknown Locations; Wedding Ceremony; Women
- Stamboul - Obélisque de Théodos - the Obelisk of Theodosius (belonged to Pharoah Thutmose III) in Istanbul, Turkey. 14.0 x 9.0 cm, 3 January 1936; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 19)
  French Writing; Hagia Sophia; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- 28 Constantine - Le Pont El Kantara - the El Kantara Bridge in Constantine, Algeria with men in military uniform walking across it. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Algeria; Bridges; French Writing; Postcards
- Constantinople - Fanaraki du Bosphore - the Anadolu Kavagı lighthouse on the Bosphorous in Constantinople. 8.6 x 13.7 cm, 12 March 1941; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Armenian Writing; Bosphorous; Constantinople; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- (Cairo) Rue Bab-El-Hadid - Bab-El-Hadid Street in Cairo, Egypt with two stamps on the front. 13.8 x 8.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Cairo, Egypt; French Writing; Postal Stamps; Postcards
- Constantinople - Vue Panoramique de Stamboul - a panoramic view of Stamboul, Constantinople. 8.7 x 13.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Blue Mosque; Bosphorous; Constantinople; French Writing; Grand Bazaar; Hagia Sophia; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- Constantinople - Eaux douces d'Asie - row boats on river with houses in the background. 8.7 x 13.7 cm, 2 March 1919; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Boats; Constantinople; French Writing; Istanbul, Turkey; Postcards
- Tel-Aviv - Boulevard Rothschild - the Rothschild Boulevard in Tel-Aviv. 9.2 x 14.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 20)
  French Writing; Postcards; Telaviv
- Femmes arabes portant de l'eau - Arab women carrying water in jugs. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Italian Writing; Postcards; Rivers; Unknown Locations; Women
- Nouvelle gare de Haidar-Pacha - Constantinople - The new Haydarpasha Train Station in Constantinople. 9.0 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Constantinople; Haydarpasa Terminal; Istanbul, Turkey; Ottoman Writing; Postcards
- 155 Alger - Les quais et le Boulevard - The docks and the main road in Algiers, Algeria. 8.7 x 13.8 cm, 18 December; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Algiers, Algeria; French Writing; Postal Stamps; Postcards
- Cairo: Mosque El Azhar - El Azhar Mosque in Cairo, Egypt. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Cairo, Egypt; Mosques; Postcards; Turkish Writing
- Jerusalem - Klagemauer - Muraille de la Lamentation des Juifs - Jewish worshippers at the Wailing Wall in Jerusalem. 9.0 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 21)
  French Writing; Jerusalem; Postcards; Religious Sites
- Maroc (Scénes et Types) Mauresque à l'heure du Thé - Moorish women at tea time in Morocco. 8.8 x 4.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 21)
  French Writing; Morocco; Postcards; Tea; The Moors; Women
- 583 - Intérieur d'une Maison Mauresque - Postcard of the interior of a Moorish house with three youths seated in the middle. Same scene different coloring as ref600. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Architecture; French Writing; Postcards; The Moors; Unknown Locations; Women
- 165 Egyptians Types and Scenes - Water Carriers - Two women carrying water in jugs with the Pyramids in the background. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, 4 December 19[-?-]; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 21)
  French Writing; Postcards; Rivers; Unknown Locations; Women
- Constantinople - Thérapia et l'ambassade de l'Allemagne - Tarabya and the Germany Embassy from the water, in Constantinople. 8.6 x 13.5 cm, 16 December 1920; Unknown (Box 3, Folder 21)